<resources>
    <string name="app_name">InquilinOs</string>
    <string name="contact">Contact us</string>
    <string name="lang">Select your language</string>
    <string name="info">Touristic information</string>
    <string name="services">Services</string>
    <string name="about">Visit our website</string>
    <string name="newLanguage">New language selected: English</string>
    <string name="catedralSantaMaria">Cathedral Santa Maria</string>
    <string name="palacioReal">Real Palace</string>
    <string name="puertaAlcala">Puerta de Alcala</string>
    <string name="cibeles">Cibeles</string>
    <string name="puertaSol">Sol</string>
    <string name="elRetiro">"Retiro\'s" Park</string>
    <string name="sanJeronimo">"San Jeronimo\'s" Church</string>
    <string name="elPrado">El Prado Museum</string>
    <string name="reinaSofia">Reina Sofia Museum</string>
    <string name="museoThyssen">Thyssen-Bornemisza Museum</string>
    <string name="plazaToros">Plaza de Toros</string>
    <string name="plazaMayor">Plaza Mayor</string>
    <string name="plazaEspania">Plaza España</string>
    <string name="mercadoSanMiguel">San Miguel Market</string>
    <string name="plazaVilla">Plaza Villa</string>
    <string name="temploDebod">Debos Temple</string>

    <string name="catedralSantaMariaExp">
        Continuing along Calle Mayor you will arrive at the "Catedral de la Almudena",
         considered the most important religious building to see in Madrid.
         Built on the remains of an ancient mosque and the first cathedral to be consecrated outside of Rome
         in 1993, by Pope John Paul II, this temple dedicated to the Virgin Mary stands out on the outside
         for its enormous dome, while the stained glass windows inside create a magical atmosphere.
    </string>
    <string name="palacioRealExp">
        Right in front of the Almudena Cathedral, in the "Plaza de la Armería",
         is the entrance to the "Palacio Real" (Royal Palace), official residence of the kings of Spain until
         moved to the "Palacio de la Zarzuela", which is also another of the best places to visit in Madrid.
         This huge palace, the largest in Western Europe, is now used for sightseeing and
         it is closed for state ceremonies and official acts and before or after entering the complex we recommend
         go to the Plaza de Oriente and above all, to the Sabatini\'s gardens, to take good photos of the palace.
</string>
    <string name="puertaAlcalaExp">
        A few meters from Plaza de Cibeles, going up Calle Alcalá,
         you will arrive at the Puerta de Alcalá, the most famous of the five ancient royal doors that gave
         access to the city and another of the most beautiful places to see in Madrid.
    </string>
    <string name="cibelesExp">
        Plaza de Cibeles, presided over by the beautiful Fuente de las Cibeles,
         venue of the Real Madrid titles, is another of the most emblematic places to visit
         in Madrid.
         In addition to observing from afar the chariot pulled by lions of the goddess Cibeles, in this roundabout you have
         several buildings to take into account such as the Palacio de Buenavista, dating from 1777, the Palacio
         de Linares, the Bank of Spain and above all the imposing Palacio de Cibeles, which houses the
         town hall and has a fantastic viewpoint on its terrace that offers visits from the Parque del
         Retreat to the skyscrapers of the financial district.
    </string>
    <string name="puertaSolExp">
        In this square there are several points of interest such as the statue
         del Oso y el Madroño (symbol of Madrid), the famous advertising poster for Tío Pepe and the statue
         equestrian of Carlos III, located right in the center.
         Although the most emblematic place in this vast space, active 24 hours a day, is the Casa
         Post Office, whose clock chimes the popular end-of-year chimes, and right next to it is a
         small granite plaque that marks the «kilometer 0» of Spain.
    </string>
    <string name="elRetiroExp">
        Another of the best things to do in Madrid is to have a pleasant
         walk through the famous Retiro Park, disconnecting from the noise and stress of the city.
         In this historical park you will find from a huge artificial pond, which has in one of the
         side the Monument to Alfonso XII and where you can rent a small boat to take a walk,
         to the beautiful Crystal Palace, which will make you fall in love at first sight.
    </string>
    <string name="sanJeronimoExp">
        The old monastery of San Jerónimo el Real, popularly known as
        "Los Jerónimos", was one of the most important monasteries in Madrid, originally governed
         by the Order of Saint Jerome. Next to it was the so-called Royal Room, later enlarged as
         Palacio del Buen Retiro in the time of Felipe IV.</string>
    <string name="elPradoExp">
        One of the most important museums in the world and another of the places that
         essential to visit in Madrid.
         With thousands of interesting works, among the best works to see in the Prado Museum are
         The Three Graces by Rubens, The Knight with the Hand on the Chest by El Greco, The Naked Maja
         and El 3 de mayo en Madrid by Goya, The Garden of Earthly Delights by El Bosco and the masterpiece
         Velazquez\'s Las Meninas.</string>
    <string name="reinaSofiaExp">
        With more than 4 million visitors a year, this museum has great
         works by Dalí and Miró, among many other artists, although nothing overshadows its jewel, the painting
         Picasso\'s Guernica, one of the great masterpieces in the history of painting.
    </string>
    <string name="museoThyssenExp">
        Located on the Paseo del Arte, its permanent collection traces history
         of European painting from the Middle Ages to the end of the 20th century. The Italian Primitives,
         the German Renaissance, 19th century American painting, Impressionism, German Expressionism
         and Russian Constructivism are the most widely represented schools and movements in
         the museum.
    </string>
    <string name="plazaTorosExp">
        With a capacity for more than 23,000 spectators, the Plaza de Toros
         de Las Ventas is the largest in Spain and the third with the largest capacity in the world, behind
         of those of Mexico and Valencia (Venezuela).
         The square, built in 1929 on the land known as
         “Las Ventas del Espíritu Santo”, was designed in neo-Mudejar style with exposed red brick
         and it has a ring of 61 meters in diameter.
    </string>
    <string name="plazaMayorExp">
        This beautiful rectangular square of 129 meters long and 94 wide,
         It is surrounded by important buildings such as the Casa de la Panadería and other jewels such as the Arco
         of Cuchilleros and the Statue of Philip III, a gift from the Duke of Florence.
    </string>
    <string name="plazaEspaniaExp">
        Although it is not the most beautiful in the city, it is worth investing a
         time to see several monuments and historic buildings such as the Tower of Madrid, 142 meters
         high, the Casa Gallardo in modernist style, the Monument to Miguel de Cervantes and the
         building of the Asturian Mining Company.
    </string>
    <string name="mercadoSanMiguelExp">
        Located in the heart of the city, the San Miguel Market is a point
         meeting point for lovers of good gastronomy and one of the most emblematic markets
         what to see in Madrid
    </string>
    <string name="plazaVillaExp">
        When you leave the San Miguel market you can take a walk through the streets of the well-known
         such as Madrid de los Austrias, in which the beautiful Plaza de la Villa stands out.
    </string>
    <string name="temploDebodExp">
        This ancient Egyptian temple over 2,200 years old was
         a gift from Egypt to Spain for the help it gave at the time to save Abu Simbel from
         be submerged under the waters of the Aswan High Dam.
         The Temple of Debod has become a beautiful place in which to enjoy the tranquility and
         relax, especially in the late afternoon, when you can watch a unique sunset.
    </string>

    <string name="events">Events</string>
    <string name="searchingEvent">Searching Events in Madrid</string>
    <string name="touristMap">Tourist Map</string>
    <string name="nextEvents">Next Events</string>
    <string name="seeInMap">See in map</string>
    <string name="goToWeb">Go to website</string>

    <string name="select_spanish" translatable="false">Spanish</string>
    <string name="select_french" translatable="false">French</string>
    <string name="select_english" translatable="false">English</string>
    <string name="content_image" translatable="false">Descriptive image</string>
    <string name="accept" translatable="false">Accept</string>
    <string name="description_img_photo" translatable="false">image</string>
    <string name="select_language" translatable="false">Select Language</string>
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment" translatable="false">Hello blank fragment</string>

    <string name="welcome">Welcome</string>
    <string name="yourStay">For your stay</string>
</resources>